Guide to the Park Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Family Papers, 1701-1929; Series II; 2.5' (6 boxes, 1 folio)
  - General
    - Park, Marion Edwards, 1875-1960
      - Correspondence
        - Edwards, Jerusha Williams (Billings), [1895?] (Box 14, Folder 185)
        - Forbes, R[ebecca?] T., 1906 (Box 14, Folder 186)
        - Lefavour, Henry, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 187)
        - Lord, Katharine, 1926-1927, undated (Box 14, Folder 188)
        - Mead, Alice, [1917] (Box 14, Folder 189)
        - Morse, Frances Rollins, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 190)
        - Park, Edwards Albert, [1895?]-1897 (Box 14, Folder 191)
        - Park, Edwards Amasa, 1897 (Box 14, Folder 192)
        - Park, Sara Billings (Edwards), 1894-[1911?], n.d (Box 14, Folder 193-200)
        - Park, William Edwards, 1884, 1896-1905 (Box 15, Folder 201)
        - Rowland, H. Edwards, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 202)
        - Strong, Anne H., 1895, 1906, [1922?] (Box 15, Folder 203)
        - Strong, Margaret, undated (Box 15, Folder 204)
        - Thomas, Martha Carey, 1913, 1921-1929, undated (Box 15, Folder 205-208)
        - Wing, Asa Shove, 1922, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 209)
        - Unidentified, [1897?], 1906, undated (Box 15, Folder 210)
      - Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 211)
      - Recollections of Edwards Amasa Park, undated (Box 15, Folder 212)
    - Park, Sara Billings (Edwards), d.1913
      - Correspondence
        - Billings, Harriet S. and Elizabeth Storrs (Billings) Mead, 1872-1873, 1905, undated (Box 15, Folder 213)
        - Coffin, Charles Albert, 1899 (Box 15, Folder 214)
        - Edwards, Jerusha Williams (Billings), 1848 (Box 15, Folder 215)
        - Forbes, [Will?], 1905 (Box 15, Folder 216)
        - Mosher, Jennie Storrs, 1879 (Box 15, Folder 217)
        - Park, Agnes, 1897, 1910 (Box 15, Folder 218)
        - Park, Edwards Albert, 1897 (Box 15, Folder 219)
        - Park, Marion Edwards, 1902 (Box 15, Folder 220)
        - Park, William Edwards., 1872-1905, n d. (Box 15, Folder 221-222)
        - Phelps, Mary A., 1876. (Box 15, Folder 223)
        - Unidentified, 1863-1878, 1897, n.d (Box 15, Folder 224)
      - Poems, 1878, undated (Box 15, Folder 225)
    - Park, William Edwards, 1837-1910
      - Correspondence
        - Coffin, Charles Albert, 1905 (Box 15, Folder 226)
        - Dexter, Franklin Bowditch, 1897 (Box 15, Folder 227)
        - Edwards, E., 1844-1945, undated (Box 15, Folder 228)
        - Edwards, Robert S., 1850 (Box 15, Folder 229)
        - Fitch, Frank S., 1904 (Box 15, Folder 230)
        - Park, Agnes, 1905 (Box 15, Folder 231)
        - Park, Edwards Albert, 1879 (Box 15, Folder 232)
        - Park, Edwards Amasa, 1877 (Box 15, Folder 233)
        - Park, Marion Edwards, 1878-1881, undated (Box 16, Folder 234)
        - Park, Sara Billings (Edwards), 1881-1901, undated (Box 16, Folder 235-236)
        - [Shodd?], J.H., 1879-1880 (Box 16, Folder 237)
        - [Tappan, S.S.?], undated (Box 16, Folder 238)
        - Unidentified, 1843, 1874, undated (Box 16, Folder 239)
      - Journal of travels in Norway, 1901 (Box 16, Folder 240)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1878, 1881, undated (Box 16, Folder 241)
      - Obituaries, 1910 (Box 16, Folder 242)
      - Poems, including valentine probably sent to WEP, 1867, 1880, 1899 (Box 16, Folder 243)
      - Printed copy of Yale Literary Magazine with WEP's DeForest Prize Oration, 1861 (Box 16, Folder 244)
    - Park family
      - Genealogical and biographical notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 245)
      - Hair samples, 1826-1831 (Box 16, Folder 245)
      - List of books deposited in Yale University Library, 1912 (Box 16, Folder 245)
      - Photographs and engravings, [1902?], undated (Box 16, Folder 246)
    - Reeve, Tapping, 1744-1823, and James Gould, 1770-1838
      - Lectures on law: notebooks kept by students at Litchfield Law School
        - Lectures by Reeve, 1792-1795 (Box 16, Folder 247)
        - Lectures by Gould and Reeve E.F., Tattnall, 1811 (Box 16, Folder 248)
    - Storrs, Sarah W.
      - Correspondence: Edwards, Jerusha Williams (Billings), and Sara Billings (Edwards) Park, 1885 (Box 16, Folder 249)
    - Unidentified
      - Diary, undated (Box 16, Folder 250)
  - Oversize
    Folio
    - Edwards, Henry, 1798-1885
      - Commission as ensign, signed by Governor DeWitt Clinton of New York, 1821 (Box 17, Folder 251)
    - Edwards, Jonathan, 1703-1758
      - ALS to Mr. Burr (photostatic copy), 1756 (Box 17, Folder 252)
    - Park, Edwards Amasa
      - Notes and documents: constitution of the Religious Society, Andover Theological Seminary, undated (Box 17, Folder 253)
      - Printed matter
        - 2 Confederate bonds, 1863, 1865 (Box 17, Folder 254)
        - Program for "Exhibition at the Hall of Day's Academy," listing a declamation of poetry by EAP, 1819 (Box 17, Folder 255)
- APPENDIX A: INDEX TO SELECTED CORRESPONDENCE
  - Abbott, Lyman (1835-1922). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Brooklyn, N.Y., June 1896 (Box 8)
  - Adams, Jasper (1793-1841). ALS to Eliphalet Pearson. Andover, Mass., March 8, 1816 (Box 4)
  - Adams, John, pres. U.S. (1735-1826). Certification with Josiah Quincy, Jr. to the testimony of the litigants in the case of Balston vs. Russell. Superior Court, Suffolk County, Mass., February term, 1772
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.34
  - Adams, John Quincy, pres. U.S. (1767-1848). ALS to Pres. James Monroe. Washington, July 8, 1818
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.42
  - Adams, Samuel (1722-1803). Receipt to Joseph Jackson. Boston, Mass., August 16, 1756
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.4
  - Adams, William (1807-1880).
    - ALS to Edwards A. Park. New York, September 22, 1873 (Box 7)
    - ALS to an unnamed person. New York, January 12, 1876 (Box 7)
  - Adelung, Johann Cristoph (1732-1806). Autograph notes in German written on ALS from an unidentified person, Meissen, May 15, 1796
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.8
  - Agassiz, Louis (1807-1873). ALS to M. Newland. Brookline, Mass., April 19, [n.y.] (Box 8)
  - Alcott, Amos Bronson (1799-1888). Graphic sayings, or his thoughts on what should be one's attitude toward one's vocation. Unsigned., undated
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.58
  - Alexander, William Lindsay (1808-1884).
    - 2 ALS to Bela Bates Edwards. Edinburgh, 1846 [no month or day]; June 1, 1848 (Box 7)
    - Autograph testimonal, signed also by William Cunningham, in favor of the Bibliotheca Sacra of which Edwards A. Park and Bela B. Edwards were editors
  - Alford, Henry (1810-1871). ALS to Henry Allon. Canterbury, England, April 8, 1868 (Box 7)
  - Alison, Sir Archibald, bart. (1792-1867).
    - AL in third person to David Bogue. Glasgow, Scotland, May 7, 1856 (Box 7)
    - Social note in the third person to the Magistrates and Town Council. County Buildings [Lanarkshire]?, June 18 [n.y.]
  - Allen, Alexamder Viets Griswold (1841-1908). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Cambridge, Mass., December 3, 1885 (Box 7)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences. ALS (draft) from Eliphalet Pearson, cor. sec., to Sir William Jones, president of the Bengal Asiatic society presenting to the latter the Memoirs of the Academy. Cambridge, Mass., February 2, 1795 (Box 2)
  - American Education Society, Boston. Printed circular quoting a resolution adopted by the Society Oct, 1829. Signed by Elais Cornelius and addressed to Samuel Farrar. Boston, Dec 1829. Boston, Mass., December 1829 (Box 6)
  - Ammon, Christoph Friedrich von (1766-1850). ALS in German to Gerhard Fleischer. Dresden, Germany, March 28, 1824
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.42
  - Argyll, George Douglas Campbell, 8th duke of (1823-1900?). ALS to an unnamed person. London, November 17, 1869 (Box 7)
  - Arnold, Mary (Penrose). ALS to Bela Bates Edwards. Totton, England, August 31, 1850 (Box 7)
  - Arnold, Matthew (1822-1888). ALS to Henry Allon. London, November 17, 1869 (Box 7)
  - Ashburton, Alexander Baring, 1st baron (1774-1848). ALS to an unnamed person. Bruton Street, undated
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.60
  - Backus, Azel (1765-1817). ALS to Tapping Reeve. [no place], March 14, 1810
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.45
  - Backus, Jonathan Trumbull (1809-1892). ALS to Henry Darling. Schenectady, N.Y., October 22, 1872 (Box 7)
  - Bancroft, George (1800-1891). 3 ALS to the Rev. Edwards A. Park. New York, June 22, 29, July 14, 1859
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.29, 31
  - Banister, William B. ALS to Benjamin B. Wisner. Brookfield, Mass., Ded 8, 1831 (Box 6)
  - Banks, W.N. ALS to Charles Tilt. Kentish Town, Middx., England, October 16 [n.y.] (Box 8)
  - Barlow, Joel (1754-1812). ALS to Tapping Reeve. Hartford, Conn., May 1, 1781 (Box 1)
  - Barnes, Albert (1798-1870). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Philadelphia, November 13, 1850
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.66
  - Barnum, Phineas Taylor (1810-1891). ALS to Olin A. Brainard. Bridgeport, Conn., December 23, 1879 (Box 7)
  - Bartlet, William (1748-1841).
    - ALS to Samuel Farrar. Newburyport, Mass., December 27, 1823 (Box 5)
    - ALS to Edwards A. Park. Newburyport, Mass., July 15, 1837
  - Bayly, Thomas Haynes (1797-1839). ALS to an unnamed person, probably a publisher, stating he is sending the second song [no place, no year]
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.31
  - Baconsfield, Benjamin Disraeli, 1st earl of (1804-1881). Note admitting bearer to the gallery of the House, May 4, 1848
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.22
  - Bean, Joseph (1718-1784). "A couple [sic] of discourses delivered at the annual fast 15 April 1773 from Revelation 3:1-2." Wrentham, Mass., April 15, 1773 (Box 7)
  - Beckwith, George Cone (1801-1870). ALS to Benjamin B. Wisner. Andover, Mass., October 5, 1831 (Box 6)
  - Beecher, Henry Ward (1813-1887). ALS to Edwards A. Park. "On a lecturing tour,", March 4 [1880]? (Box 7)
  - Bellamy, Joseph (1719-1790).
    - AL (signed with initials) to the New York Presbytery. Woodbury, Conn., [July 1754] (Box 1)
    - ALS to the Rev. Stephen West. Bethlem, Conn., February 6, 1785 (Box 1)
  - Belshah, Thomas (1750-1829). ALS to an unnamed person. Daventry, [Northants., Eng.], October 31, 1782
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.9
  - Beman, Nathan Sidney Smith (1785-1871). ALS to an unnamed person. Troy, N.Y., September 25, 1869 (Box 7)
  - Benton, Thomas Hart (1782-1858). AL in third person to the President [Polk] concerning someone recommended by the Rev. Mr. James Oliver Van de Velde as suitable to go to New Mexico. Washington, [1846]
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.38
  - Blacque, bey, Turkish minister to U.S. ALS to Amory Edwards. Washington, November 26, 1872 (Box 7)
  - Blatchford, Edgcumbe H. ALS to Edward Buck. New York, March 22, 1847 (Box 7)
  - Bliss, George (1764-1830). ALS to Samuel Ferrar. Springfield, Mass., October 27, 1815 (Box 4)
  - Blumenbach, Johann Friedrich (1752-1840). Unsigned inscription in Latin to Blumenbach.
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.11
  - Boettiger, Karl August (1760-1835).
    - ALS in German to Gerhard Fleischer. Dresden, Germany, November 3, 1825
    - ALS in French to Schulz. Dresden, Germany, July 2, 1815
  - Boudinot, Elias (1740-1821). ALS to John T. Kempe. Elizabethtown, N.J., August 30, 1774
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.4
  - Bowditch, Nathaniel (1773-1838). ALS to Miss E. Clarke. Boston, Mass., April 27, 1831
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.25
  - Bowen, Francis (1811-1890). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Cambridge, Mass., July 9, 1876 (Box 7)
  - Bowring, Sir John (1792-1872). Letter in third person to Henry Enfield. 5 Jeffrey Square, January 21, 1826
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.33
  - Breckinridge, John (1797-1841). ALS to B.B. Wisner. Baltimore, May 21, 1831 (Box 6)
  - Breckinridge, Robert Jefferson (1800-1871). ALS to William L. Breckinridge. Kexington, Ky., June 29, 1863 (Box 7)
  - Bridgman, Elijah Coleman (1801-1861). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Boston, August 26, 1852
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.68
  - Bridgman, Laura Dewey (1829-1889). ALS to Abby [last name not given]. "Sunny Home" i.e. Perkins Institution, Boston, December 2, 1855
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.65
  - Brigham, David. ALS to Edwards A. Park. Randolph, Mass., December 13, 1831 (Box 6)
  - Brocq, Jean Charlemagne. ALS to Edwards A. Park. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., June 13, 1899 (Box 8)
  - Broglie, Albertine Ida Gustavine de Stael, duchesse de (1797-1838). ALS in French to Frédéric Joél Jean Gérard Monod. Paris, February 1, 1834
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.48
  - Brooks, Peter Chardon (1767-1849). ALS to John Watson. Boston, February 27, 1811
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.50
  - Brooks, Phillips (1835-1893). 3 ALS to Edwards A. Park. Boston and North Andover, Mass., June 24, 1871; April 23, 1879 (Box 7)
  - Brougham, William Brougham, 2nd baron (1795-1886). ALS to Sir [an unnamed person]. Glasgow, undated
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.15
  - Brown, John (1784-1858).
    - ALS to Bela Bates Edwards. Edinburgh, May 15, 1848 (Box 7)
    - Testimonial in favor of the Bibliotheca Sacra, sent probably to Bela Bates Edwards. Edinburgh, June 30, 1846 (Box 7)
  - Brown, John (1810-1882). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Edinburgh, November 12, 1869 (Box 7)
  - Brown, Thomas. Copy of letter to William McCullock. Boston, December 13, 1743 (Box 1)
  - Brown University, Providence, R.I. Acknowledgment to Edwards A. Park of receipt of book presented by him to the Library. Signed by Francis Wayland, President and R.A. Guild, Librarian. Providence, January 19, 1850 (Box 7)
  - Brunswick, Friedrich Wilhelm, duke of (1771-1815). Grant of 2 Thaler to Elisabeth Ledmacher, written in German. Braunschweig, March 4, 1815
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.4
  - Bryant, William Cullen (1794-1873). ALS to an unnamed person. New York, September 2, 1846
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.8
  - Bryce, James Bryce, viscount (1838-1922). ALS to Henry Robert Reynolds. London, December 12, [n.y. - 1868?] (Box 8)
  - Buchanan, James, pres. U.S. (1791-1868). ALS to William L. Marcy. Washington, June 22, 1846
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.60
  - Buckminster, Joseph (1751-1812). ALS to Eliphalet Pearson. Portsmouth, N.H., August 10, 1804 (Box 2)
  - Burder, Henry Forster (1783-1864). ALS to the Rev. Edwards A. Park. Hackney, [Middx.], October 12, 1843
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.42
  - Burgess, George (1809-1866). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Gardiner, Me., September 17, 1862 (Box 7)
  - Burgess, Sophia (KIP). ALS to the editors of Bibliotheca Sacra, Gardiner, Me., November 1, 1870 (Box 7)
  - Burns, Robert (1759-1796). Fragment concerning examination of stocks of old ale, possibly in his capacity as exciseman. Dumfries, Scotland, [1792?]
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.3
  - Burr, Aaron (1756-1836).
    Transcripts of letters next to original, in chronological order.
    - ALS to Timothy Edwards. New York, July 3, 1788 (Box 1)
    - 13 ALS from Sarah (Burr) Reeve. From various places:
      - 1773 August 27; September 8; [2 circa Oct] (Box 1)
      - 1774 January 17/20, 31 (Box 1)
      - 1775 Jul; September 18, 24 (Box 1)
      - 1776 July 1 (Box 1)
      - 1777 June 28 (Box 1)
      - [1778] November 5 (Box 1)
      - [1780 October 6]? (Box 1)
    - 8 ALS to Tapping Reeve. From various places:
      - 1775 August 2 (Box 1)
      - [1776] May 22 (Box 1)
      - 1780 July 5 (Box 1)
      - 1783 January 18; [ca. Aug]; September 14 (Box 1)
      - 1785 December 10 (Box 1)
      - 1813 August 21
        See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.13
    - "A Creed." (attributed author), n.p., undated
  - Burr, Annabella (Shedden) Reeve (1789-1849). ALS to Tapping Reeve. Richmond, Va., September 16, 1812 (Box 3)
  - Burr, Eunice (Dennie) (1729-1805). 6 ALS to Sarah (Burr) Reeve. Fairfield, Conn:
    - 1773 Feb; April 6 (Box 1)
    - 1774 January 17; April 6; July 7; December 27 (Box 1)
  - Burr, Thaddeus (1735-1801). 2 ALS to Tapping Reeve. Fairfield, Conn:
    - 1787 September 13 (Box 1)
    - undated (Box 8)
  - Burr, Theodosia (Barstow) Prevost (1746-1794).
    - 3 ALS to Sarah (Burr) Reeve. Sharon, Conn., 1780 [October 9?], December 2; undated
    - 3 ALS to Tapping Reeve and Sarah (Burr) Reeve. [no place], [1794]; undated
  - Buxton, Thomas Fowell (1786-1845). ALS to Joseph Lancaster. Spita Vielos School, December 13, 1811
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.11
  - Byles, Mather (1706/7-1788). Autograph list of persons married by Byles in 1736. Boston
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.23
  - Byron, Anne Isabella Noel (Milbank) lady. ALS to Mme. Mojon. Fontainebleau., August 31 [n.y.]
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.34
  - Byron, George Gordon, 6th baron (1788-1824). Poem, entitled "Espression" attributed to Byron but not in his hand, December 13, 1811 (Box 8)
  - Cairns, John. ALS to an unnamed person. Berwick, April 20, 1830 (Box 6)
  - Calderwood, Henry (1830-1897). 2 ALS to Edwards A. Park. Edinburgh and Merchiston, Scotland, November 12, 1869; June 11, 1872 (Box 7)
  - Candish, Robert Smith (1806-1873). ALS to Bela Bates Edwards. Edinburgh, Saturday [1846] (Box 7)
  - Canning, George (1770-1827). Letter in third person to Lady Peshall. [London], June 5, 1827
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.16
  - Carey, Mathew (1760-1839). ALS to Daniel Srute. Philadelphia, April 3, 1815
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.44
  - Cass, Lewis (1782-1866). ALS to Cov. William Learned Marcy. [n.p.], January 17, [n.y.]
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.44
  - Chalmers, Thomas (1780-1847). Note of regards, apparently, enclosed with something, to:
    - Bela Bates Edwards and family. [n.p.], June 29, 1846 (Box 7)
    - ALS to Bp. John Strachan. Near Selkirk, May 10, 1833
  - Channing, William Ellery (1780-1842). 2 ALS to Edwards A. Park. Boston:
    - February 11, 1840 (Box 7)
    - January 6, 1841
  - Chaplin, Calvin (1763-1851). ALS to Samuel Farrar. Rocky Hill, Conn., March 1, 1848 (Box 7)
  - Charles, Prince of Prussia. LS in French to ____. St. Petersburg, Russia, April 6, 1837
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.56
  - Chase, Ira (1793-1864). ALS to Eliphalet Pearson. Andover, Mass., December 19, 1816 (Box 4)
  - Choate, Rufus (1799-1859). Illegible manuscript, not a letter. [n.p.], undated
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.54
  - Christlieb, Theodor (1833-1889). ALS to an unnamed person. Bonn, Prussia, June 7, 1888 (Box 7)
  - Clark, Edward Lord (1838-1910). ALS to Edwards A. Park. [n.p.], March 18, 1893 (Box 8)
  - Clark, Thomas March (1812-1903). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Providence, R.I., June 3, 1878 (Box 7)
  - Clarkson, Thomas (1760-1846). ALS to Robinson Kitchener. Playford Hall [Suffolk, Eng.], December 10, 1822
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.14
  - Clay, Henry (1777-1852). ALS to William Edwards. Ashland, Ky., May 11, 1841
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.28
  - Cobbett, William (1763-1835). ALS to Asbury Dickins. New York, April 2, 1819
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.39
  - Codman, John (1782-1847). ALS to Herman Humphrey. Dorchester, Mass., June 25, 1843 (Box 7)
  - Colyan, Benjamin (1673-1747). Autograph list for Joseph Prout, Boston Town Clerk, of persons married by Colman in 1720. Boston
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.22
  - Colt, Peter (1744-1824). ALS to Tapping Reeve. New Haven, December 16, 1773 (Box 1)
  - Combe, George (1788-1858). ALS to Benjamin Silliman, introducing the Rev. Thomas Spencer. Edinburgh, November 24, 1845
    Transferred to Silliman Papers, MS 450.
  - Constable, Archibald (1774-1827). ALS to an unnamed person. Edinburgh, July 5, 1810
  - Constant, Alphonse Louis, (1810?-1875?). ALS in French to Frédéric Monod. [n.p.], [undated]
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5?, p.60
  - Cook, George (1772-1845). Autograph.
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.6
  - Cooper, James Fenimore (1789-1851). ALS to an unnamed person. Otsego Hall, Cooperstown [N.Y.], October 7, 1843
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.6
  - Cooper, Thomas (1759-1839). ALS to William Campbell Preston. Columbia, S.C., March 7, 1836
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.45
  - Cooper, William (1754-1809). ALS to Stephen Lusk. [n.p.], January 23, 1792
  - Cornelius, Elias (1794-1832). 4 ALS to Samuel Farrar. Boston, December 29, 1829; 1830, January 14, 15, August 17 (Box 6)
  - Corpie, George Elwes (1793-1885). ALS to Mr. Laycock. Cambridge, October 12, 1847
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.55
  - Cotton, John (1584-1652). Fragment of a sermon. [n.p.], undated
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.4
  - Crawford, Thomas Jackson (1812-1875). ALS to the Rev. Prof. Charteris. Edinburgh, November 13, 1869 (Box 7)
  - Croly, George (1780-1860). Part of ALS showing autograph.
  - Crosby, Howard (1826-1891). ALS to Dr. Darling (probably Charles Chauncey Darling). New York, April 20, 1847 (Box 7)
  - Cruikshank, George (1792-1878). ALS to Charles Tilt. London, undated (Box 8)
  - Cunningham, Allan (1785-1842). "Hme, Hame, Hame." Poem in Scottish dialect., undated
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.4
  - Cunningham, William (1805-1861). ALS to Bela Bates Edwards. Edinburgh, April 11, 1851 (Box 7)
  - Cuvier, Charles Frédéric (1798-). ALS in French to ____. Paris, August 4, 1848 (Box 7)
  - Davidson, Randall Thomas, bp. of Winchester (1848-). LS to the Rev. W. E. Park. Farnham, Surrey, Eng., February 5, 1903 (Box 8)
  - Davies, Samuel (1743-1761). ALS to an unnamed person, probably Jonathan Edwards (1703-1758). Hanover, Va., August 26, 1750 (Box 1)
  - Davis, William, Jr. ALS to Edwards Amasa Park. Boston, April 3, 1849
  - Day, Jeremiah (1773-1867).
    - ALS to an unnamed person. New York, January 17, 1823
    - ALS to Samuel Farrar. New Haven, November 3, 1829 (Box 6)
  - Depew, Chauncey Mitchell (1834-1928). LS to William E. Park. New York, March 19, 1891 (Box 8)
  - De Witt, Clinton (1769-1828). ALS to the President of the Senate. Albany, April 2, 1825
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.24
  - Dodge, Mary Abigail (1833-1896).
    - AL signed Gail Hamilton to Agnes Park. Hamilton, Mass., [June circa 1865] (Box 7)
    - ALS to Edwards A. Park. Hamilton, Mass., October 1, 1881 (Box 7)
  - Don, David (1800-1841). ALS to an unnamed person. London, January 2, 1837
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.48
  - Donald, Elijah Winchester (1848-1904). ALS to Agnes Park. Boston, January 27, 1899 (Box 8)
  - Donning, Andrew Jackson (1812-1852). ALS to Luther Tucker. Newburgh, [N.Y.], November 2, [1848]
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.56
  - Duff, Alexander (1806-1878). ALS to the Rev. Frédéric Monod. [n.p.], May 27, 1852
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.54
  - Duller, Eduard (1809-1853. Announcement in German of the dispatch of a book by post to Justimus Kerner; probably accompanied the book. Darmstadt, Germany, November 3, 1844
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.27
  - Duncan, Henry (1774-1846). ALS to the Rev. Thomas Murray. Dunfries, Scotland, May 10, 1820
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.44
  - Dunlop, John. ALS to Bela Bates Edwards. Edinburgh, June 30, 1846 (Box 7)
  - Dupin, André Marie Jean Jacques (1783-1865). Social note in French, signed, to the Baron de Vill__?. [n.p.], June 6? [n.y.]
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.3
  - Eadin, John (1810-1876). ALD probably to Edwards A. Park. Glasgow, April 23, 1871 (Box 7)
  - East, Timothy. ALS to an unnamed person. [n.p.], August 24, 1850
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.56
  - Eastburn, Manton (1801-1872). ALS commending the Christian Witness and Church Advocate to the members of the Episcopal Church in the Diocese of Massachusetts, with concurring autograph signed statements by William Nicholson, Alex H. Vietor, Phillips Brooks, and Abraham McGuire. Boston, March 11/15, 1870 (Box 7)
  - Eckley, Joseph (1750-1811). ALS to Eliphalet Pearson. Boston, [March 13, 1806] (Box 3)
  - Edgeworth, Maria (1767-1849). AL from the MS of Helen, apparently a draft. Signed on verso.
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.26
  - Edwards, Jonathan (1703-1758).